老爸要我们继承他的遗志
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things, the family business.
你知道关于萨姆 和其他孩子的秘密了
You know the truth about Sammy and the other children?
- 是的 已经有段日子了 - 爸爸 那个魔鬼
- I've known for a while. - Dad, you know the demon.
说对我和跟我一样的孩子们早有安排
Said he had plans for me and children like me.
你知道他是什么意思吗？
Do you have any idea what he meant?
不知道
No, I don't.
他跟你说了什么吗？
Did he say anything to you?
没有
No.
什么都没说
Nothing.
马克斯 你的能力是从六七个月前开始的 对吧？
Max, your abilities they started six, seven months ago, right?
- 你怎么知道？- 我的也是那时开始的
- How'd you know? - That's when mine started.
你和我 我们是被选中的
You and I were chosen.
- 为了什么？- 我不知道
- For what? - I don't know.
他们每个都可能杀人 每一个 也许这就是魔鬼想要的
Everyone's capable of murder. That's what the demon's doing.
逼迫我们 千方百计让我们崩溃
Pushing us to break us.
我们还不知道那魔鬼想要什么呢
We don't know what the demon wants.
- 我们都有某种能力 - 能力？
- We all have some kind of ability. - Ability?
某种超自然的能力 我能看到幻觉 或者说前兆
Psychic ability. I have visions, premonitions.
跟别人的都不同
It's different for everybody.
那个魔鬼说他对我们这样的人有所安排
The demon said he had plans for us.
什么样的安排？我们不知道
- What kind of plans? - I don't really know for sure.
别害怕 斯科特 你可以告诉我一切 你知道
Don't be afraid, Scott. You can tell me anything, you know that.
不管你说了什么 都仅限于你我知道
Whatever you say won't leave this room.
大概是一年多前开始的
It started a little over a year ago.
先是偏头疼
Migraines at first.
然后就发现我干些事了
Then I found I could do stuff.
「干些事」是什么意思？
What do you mean, "do stuff"?
我有一种能力
I have this ability.
如果我想的话 我能电死我所接触的任何东西
When I touch something, I can electrocute it if I want.
你怎么知道的？
How do you know?
我在邻居家的猫身上试过
I did it to the neighbor's cat.
它的内脏被电成了烤汉堡
Its insides fried up like a hamburger.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
我相信你是当真的
I believe that you believe it.
那来吧
Then here.
你想握下吗？
Wanna shake on it?
斯科特 你为什么要杀死邻居的猫？
Why would you want to kill the neighbor's cat?
我不想
I don't.
他让我干的 还不准我停下
He wants me to. And he doesn't want me to stop there.
他是谁？
Who?
黄眼睛的男人
The yellow-eyed man.
他在我的梦里出现
He comes to me in my dreams.
让我干那些事 可怕的事
Tells me to do things. Awful things.
但我拒绝了
But I tell him no.
不 我不想
No, I don't want to.
黄眼睛的人还说了什么？
What else does the yellow-eyed man tell you?
他… 他说他对我有某种安排 什么样的安排？
- He has plans for me. - What kind of plans?
有人吗？
Hello?
[邪恶力量 第2季第10集]
老爸死前 他 他告诉了我一些事
Before Dad died, he… He told me something.
关于你的
Something about you.
什么？
What?
迪恩 他跟你说了什么？
Dean, what did he tell you?
他说他…
He said that he…
要我看好你…
wanted me to watch out for you…
照顾你
take care of you.
- 这话他都说过很多遍了 - 但这次不同
- He told you that a million times. - This time was different.
他说我得…
He said that I had to…
挽救你
save you.
为什么？
Save me from what?
他就说我得救你 别的都无关紧要
He just said that I had to save you. That nothing else mattered.
如果我不能 我就…
And that if I couldn't, I'd
你就怎么样 迪恩？
You'd what, Dean?
我就得杀了你
I'd have to kill you.
他说我也许不得不杀了你 萨姆
He said that I might have to kill you, Sammy.
杀了我？
Kill me?
- 这话什么意思？- 我不知道
- What the hell's that supposed to mean? - I don't know.
肯定有什么原因他才这么说的
He must've had some reason for saying it, right?
他知道那个魔鬼对我的安排是什么吗？
Did he know the demon's plans for me?
我会站到邪恶一方还是什么？
Am I supposed to go dark side?
他还跟你说了什么 迪恩？
What else did he say?
- 就这些了 我发誓 - 你为什么不告诉我？
- Nothing, I swear. - How could you not have told me?
- 因为老爸求我不要告诉你 - 我不管
- It was Dad. He begged me not to. - Who cares?
你也别想逃避责任 迪恩
Take some responsibility for yourself, Dean.
- 你凭什么瞒着我 - 你以为我愿意？
- You had no right to keep this from me. - You think I wanted this?
我倒希望他从没这么讲过
I wish to God he'd never opened his mouth.
这样我的脑子 就不用天天想着它了
That I wouldn't have to walk around with this screaming in my head all day.
我们得搞清楚
We just gotta figure out…
是怎么回事 还有这话是什么意思
what's going on then, what the hell all this means.
是吗？
We do?
我想过了 我们应该避一阵
I've been thinking about this. I think we should just lay low.
至少是这段时间 这样安全点
At least for a while. Be safer.
- 这样我就能搞清楚… - 搞清楚什么？
- And that way I can make sure. - What?
我不会变成魔鬼？
That I don't turn evil?
- 还是我不会变成杀人凶手？- 我没这么说过
- That I don't turn into a killer? - I never said that.
天哪迪恩 你要是不小心点的话 说不定哪天会被我杀了
You're not careful, you will have to waste me one day.
我没这么说过
I never said that!
见鬼 萨姆 事情全乱套了
This whole thing is spinning out of control, all right?
你对那些莫名其妙的魔鬼病毒免疫
You're immune to some weirdo demon virus…
我也不知道该怎么办了
and I don't even know what the hell anymore.
你生我的气 我知道 没关系 我活该
You're pissed at me and I get it. That's fine. I deserve it.
但咱们应该避避风头 想想该怎么办 好吗？
But we lay low until we figure out our next move, okay?
没门
Forget it.
萨姆 求你了 嘿 求求你了
Sam, please, man. Hey, please.
再给我点时间
Just give me some time.
让我好好想想 好吗？算我求你了 好吗？
Give me some time to think, okay? I'm begging you. Please, man, please.
宝贝？
Honey?
你还好吗？
Oh. Are you okay?
哦 只是又做了一个恶梦 我很好 没事的
Oh, I just had another nightmare. It's fine, it's nothing.
- 继续睡吧 - 你确定？
- Just go back to sleep. - Are you sure?
- 是的 - 那好
- Yeah. - Okay.
- 萨姆 - 嗨 埃伦
- Sam. - Hey, Ellen.
- 你看到我好象一点不吃惊 - 你哥哥打过电话
- Don't seem surprised to see me. - Your brother's calling. Worried sick.
- 他在到处找你 - 我就知道
- Looking for you. - Yeah, I figured he might.
你们俩怎么回事？
What's going on between you two?
嗯…
So, um…
乔还好吗？
how's Jo?
- 我可不知道 - 什么意思？
- Well, I don't really know. - What do you mean?
我好几星期没见过她了 她有时候寄个明信片什么的
I haven't seen her in weeks. She sends a postcard now and again.
发生了什么？
Well, what happened?
上次和你们俩猎鬼之后
Well, after she worked that job with you boys…
她就决定继续干下去
she decided she wanted to keep on hunting.
我告诉她在我眼皮底下想都别想 她就说 好啊
I said, "Not under my roof." And she said, "Fine."
看来我是你现在最不想看到的人了
So I'm probably the last person you wanna see right now.
哦 别误会了
Oh, don't get me wrong.
我真希望能怪在你们头上
I wish I could blame the hell out of you boys.
这样能让我轻松些
It'd be easier.
可事实是 不是你们的错
Truth is, it's not your fault.
萨姆
Sam…
你们都没有错
none of it is.
我想让你知道
I want you to know that…
我很久以前就原谅你们的爸爸了…
I forgave your daddy a long time ago…
比尔的事
for what happened to my Bill.
他只是不能原谅自己
I just don't think he ever forgave himself.
到底发生了什么？
What did happen?
呃 那你来这儿有什么事？
Um. So why did you come here, sweetie?
我需要帮助
I need help.
要我找什么 萨姆？
What am I looking for, Sam?
其他人… 其他跟我一样有超能力的人
Other people…Other psychics like me.
越多越好 我要你在全国范围内找
As many as possible. And I need a nationwide search.
可我以为不可能都找到
But I thought there was no way to track them all down.
不是所有的都和你一样 在婴儿时遭遇过火灾
Not all of them had nursery fires like you did.
没错 不过有些是的 就从他们开始
Well, no, but some had to. Start there.
好了 搞定了
Done and done.
- 真够快的 - 当然了 我就是干这个的
- That was fast. - Well, apparently, that's my job.
小意思了
Make a monkey dance at the keyboard.
快说你找到什么了 阿什
Just tell us what you got, Ash.
全国共有四个符合要求的家伙
Four folks fit the profile, nationwide.
出生于1983 母亲在婴儿时就死于火灾 等等
Born in '83. Mother died in a nursery fire, the whole shebang.
4个？就这些？
Four? That's it?
堪萨斯州劳伦斯的萨姆·温彻斯特
Sam Winchester from Lawrence, Kansas.
密歇根萨吉诺的马克斯·米勒
Max Miller from Saginaw, Michigan.
俄克拉荷马州格斯里的安得烈·加拉赫
Andrew Gallagher from Guthrie, Oklahoma.
还有一个 斯库特·凯里
And, uh, another name, Scott Carey.
- 什么？你有地址吗？- 算是吧
- You got an address? - Kind of.
印第安纳州拉法叶的阿伯山公墓 486号墓室
The Arbor Hills Cemetery in Lafayette, Indiana. Plot 486.
- 他死了？- 大约一个月以前被杀
- So he's dead? - Killed about a month ago.
- 怎么死的？- 被捅死的
- Killed how? - Stabbed.
在停车场
In a parking lot.
条子们没找到什么线索 没有嫌疑人
Fuzz don't have much. No suspects.
好吧
All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你去哪儿？- 印第安纳
- Where are you going? - Indiana.
萨姆
Sam?
我得告诉迪恩 我得让他知道你在哪儿
I gotta call Dean, let him know where you are.
埃伦 我要知道我到底是什么人
Ellen, I'm trying to find answers about who I am.
而我哥哥… 他是好意 可是他没法保护我
My brother means well, but he can't protect me from that.
求你了
Please.
你说你和斯科特是高中同学？
You said you went to high school with Scott?
呃 是的 先生
Uh. Yes, sir, I did.
我刚听说这件事 很遗憾
I just heard about what happened. I'm so sorry.
斯科特是个好孩子
Scotty was a good boy.
他和你们认识的时候可大不一样了
But he changed a lot since you knew him.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
大概从一年前开始吧 他先是头疼
It started about a year ago with these headaches…
然后就得了抑郁症 妄想症 还做恶梦
then he got depressed, paranoid, nightmares.
恶梦？
Nightmares?
呃 他跟你谈起过这些噩梦吗？比如他梦到了什么？
Um. Did he ever talk to you about his nightmares? What he saw?
没有
No, no.
他从不告诉我
He closed up on me.
我想帮他 可是没用
I tried to get him help but nothing took.
他…
He'd just…
整天把自己锁在房间里
lock himself in his room for days.
我能看看他的房间吗？
Do you think maybe I could see his room?
- 你是谁？- 请别…
- Who are you? - Please.
你有危险了
You're in danger.
听着 我知道这听起来难以置信
Okay, look, I know how all this sounds…
但我既不是疯子也没磕药
but I'm not insane and I'm not on drugs.
告诉你 我很正常 这对我来说也太太奇怪了
Okay? I'm normal. This is way, way off the map for me.
好了 好了
All right, all right, just…
冷静一点 好吗？
just calm down, okay?
- 你叫什么名字？- 阿瓦
- What's your name? - Ava.
- 阿瓦？- 阿瓦·威尔森
- Ava? - Ava Wilson.
阿瓦 我是萨姆·温彻斯特
Ava, I'm Sam Winchester, all right?
现在跟我说说你的那些梦
Now, you were telling me about these dreams of yours?
哦 是啊 呃
Oh, yeah, uh, okay-
大概一年之前 我开始 头疼 然后就…
About a year ago I started having these, like, headaches and just…
开始做恶梦
nightmares, I guess.
开始我根本没多想 直到我梦到
I didn't think much of it, until I had this one dream…
一个人在停车场里被刺死
where I saw this guy get stabbed in a parking lot.
- 什么时候的事？- 嗯 大概一个月以前
- When was this? - Uh, about a month ago, but anyway-
但几天之后…
A couple of days later…
我看到了这个
I found this.
在几天前我就预见了这个人的死
I saw this guy die. Days before it happened.
我不知道是怎么回事 我不知道
I don't know why, I don't know-It's just, some reason…
不知为什么 我的梦变成了真事
my dreams are coming true.
然后昨天晚上 我又做了一个恶梦
And last night, I had another one.
- 然后？- 是关于你的
- Okay. - About you.
我看到你死了
I saw you die.
- 你怎么找到我的？- 哦 呃
- How did you find me? - Oh, uh…
你拿着旅馆的信纸 我就用谷歌找到这个旅馆 是真的
You had motel stationery. And I Googled the motel and it was real.
所以我想应该来警告你
And so I just thought that I should warn you.
真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
哦 你当然不信了 总你觉得我是个彻底的神经病
Of course you don't. You think I'm a total nut job.
不 不是的 我的意思是 你肯定也是我们中的一个
Wait, no, no, no, I mean, you must be one of us.
不好意思 什么中的一个？
Sorry. One of-One of who?
像我一样 有超能力的人中的一个
One of the psychics like me.
阿瓦 我也能看到预兆
Look, Ava, I have visions too, all right?
所以 所以我们之间是有某种关系的
So-So we're connected.
看来… 你才是个疯子 真是太棒了
Okay, so you're nuts. That's great.
好吧 好吧 你母亲是不是也是死在火灾里？
No, okay, okay, look, did your mother happen to die in a house fire?
没有 我妈妈在棕榈海滩活的好好的
No, my mother lives in Palm Beach.
那么你也不是那种模式的
So you don't fit the pattern either.
- 什么？- 我是埃伦
- Hello? - It's Ellen.
- 嗨 你有萨姆的消息吗？- 有
- Hey, have you heard from Sam? - I have.
但他让我发誓不告诉你
But he made me promise not to tell you where he is.
别这样埃伦 求你了 也许要出什么大事了
Come on, Ellen. Something bad could be going on here…
我发誓要照顾那孩子的
and I swore I'd look after that kid.
俗话说的好 你没法保护你爱的人一辈子
They say you can't protect your loved ones forever.
而要我说让它见鬼去 要不还叫什么家人？
Well, I say screw that. What else is family for?
他在印第安娜的拉法叶
He's in Lafayette, Indiana.
谢谢
Thanks.
你干嘛不在被炸死之前 离开这儿呢？
Why can't you just leave town? Please, before you blow up?
不行
No, I can't.
天哪 为什么？
Oh, God. Why not?
因为这儿有事发生 阿瓦 和你我都有关
Because there's something going on here, Ava.
我是说 还有其他跟我们一样的人
With you. With me. I mean, there are others like us out there.
我们都陷入了某种件事中
And we're all a part of something.
我要搞清楚到底怎么回事
And I gotta figure out what.
告诉你
Okay, you know what?
老兄 你见鬼去吧 因为我在皮奥里亚当秘书
Screw you, buddy, okay? Because I'm a secretary from Peoria.
我和其它的事情一点关系都没有 看见这个了吗？
And I'm not part of anything. Do you see this?
再过8周我就结婚了
I am getting married in eight weeks.
我应该在家里写请柬
I'm supposed to be home addressing invitations.
说起来我的进度已经严重落后了
Which I'm way behind on, by the way.
但我却开车这么远 来救你这个怪胎的小命
But instead, I drove out here to save your weirdo ass.
要是你宁可呆在这儿等死 随你的便
But if you just wanna stay here and die, fine.
而我？我要回到正常人的生活去了
Me, I'm due back on planet Earth.
难道你不想知道是怎么回事？
Don't you wanna know why this is happening?
我是说 你难道不害怕这些幻觉吗？
I mean, don't these visions scare the hell out of you?
因为如果你现在走出门
Because if you walk out that door right now…
就可能永远蒙在鼓里了
you might never know the truth.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
那么 威尔逊小姐 你是新来的？
So, Miss Wilson, you're new in town?
对
That's right.
你为什么来做心理治疗呢？
And what made you decide to seek out therapy?
- 我也不知道 - 你不知道？
- I have no idea. - No?
不 我是说 我现在真的觉得
No. I mean, I'm feeling really super…
非常… 特别… 不安
anxious, right now.
还有别的吗？
Okay, anything else?
呃…
Uh…
- 活见鬼 - 什么？
- Holy crap. - What?
我刚刚想起来 我小时候吞了 大概8块Pop Rock糖
I just remembered when I was a kid, I swallowed eight things of Pop Rocks…
又喝了一整桶可乐
and drank a can of Coke.
你觉得那算是有自杀的倾向吗？
You don't think that counts as a suicide attempt, do you?
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
- 我有没有事？- 对
- Am I okay? - Yeah.
我刚刚帮你 偷了个死人的保密心理档案
I just helped you steal some dead guy's confidential psych files.
我太厉害了
I'm awesome.
大概是一年多前开始的
It started a little over a year ago.
先是偏头疼
Migraines at first.
然后就发现我能干些事了
Then I found that I could do stuff.
「干些事」是什么意思？
What do you mean, "do stuff"?
我有一种能力
I have this ability.
如果我想的话 我能电死我所接触的任何东西
When I touch something, I can electrocute it if I want.
感谢上帝 你没事
Thank God you're okay.
喔 不只是没事 萨姆 你这个小狐狸
Oh, you're better than okay. Sam, you sly dog.
那个黄眼男人还说了什么？
What else does the yellow-eyed man say?
他为我计划好了
He has plans for me.
说是会有一场战争
He says there's a war coming.
像我这样的人就会变成战士
And people like me, we're gonna be the soldiers.
一切都将改变
Everything is about to change.
他说的人里面不包括我们吧 是吗？
He's not talking about us, right?
我想是的
Yeah, I think he is.
那我们如何变成他想要的人？
Well-But how can we turn into that?
我不…
I don't…
趴下 上帝啊
Get down. Oh, my God.
- 告诉我怎么回事？- 趴下
Tell me what's happening! Stay low.
萨姆
Sam.
戈登
Gordon.
你这么对我弟弟的话 我就杀了你
You do that to my brother? I'll kill you.
迪恩 等一下
Dean, wait.
等一下 我不太明白 我们为什么不报警呢？
Wait, I don't understand. Shouldn't we be talking to the cops?
相信我 那样做对我们没什么好处
Trust me, they wouldn't do us much good.
这是2。-233直径的子弹 亚音速的
These are.223 caliber. Subsonic rounds.
这家伙肯定在枪上安装了消声音器
The guy must have put a suppressor on the rifle.
嘿 你是谁？
Dude, who are you?
我只是… 嗯 经常看T。-J·胡克的节目
Uh, I just-I just, uh, watch a lot of T.J. Hooker.
- 打电话给谁？- 我哥
- Who are you calling? - My brother.
我们需要帮助
I think we definitely need help.
- 哈喽？- 迪恩
- Hello? - Dean.
萨姆我一直在找你
Sam, I've been looking for you.
听着 我现在在印地安那拉斐特
Yeah, uh, look, I'm in Indiana, uh, Lafayette.
- 我知道 - 你知道？
- I know. - You do?
是的 我找埃伦过了 我自己过来的
Yeah, I talked to Ellen. I just got here myself.
真是个有趣的小镇
It's a real funky town.
你甩了我萨姆
You ditched me, Sammy.
是的 抱歉了
Yeah, I'm sorry.
- 听着 现在有人在跟踪我 什么？- 是谁？
- look, um…right now, there's someone after me. - What? Who?
我不清楚 我要你帮我找出是谁
I don't know. That's what we need to find out.
你在哪？
Where are you?
我现在住在门罗路5637号 你过来和我碰个头吧？
I'm staying at 5637 Monroe Street. Why don't you meet me here?
好的
Yeah, sure.
这样做难吗？
Now, was that so hard?
少来了
Bite me.
- 怎么了？- 我哥有麻烦了
- What is it? - My brother's in trouble.
什么？
What?
他给我了一个暗号
He gave me a code word.
有人用枪指着他
Someone's got a gun on him.
- 暗号？- 是的 有趣的小镇
- Code word? - Yeah, funky town.
他想出来的
Well, he thought of it.
说来话长了 走吧
It's kind of a long story. Come on.
戈登
Gordy.
我知道我和萨姆不讨你喜欢
I know me and Sam aingt exactly your favorite people.
但… 你也太极端了吧
But don't you think this is a little extreme?
喔 你认为这是为了报复吗？
What, you think this is revenge?
我们只是让你绑着 在那推垃圾里面待了三天而已
We did leave you tied up in your own mess for three days…
那是个不错主意吧 不好意思 我不该笑的
ha-ha, which was awesome. I'm sorry, I shouldn't laugh.
是的
Yeah.
为这事 我是想好好的教训你一下
I was planning on whupping your ass for that.
但并不是为了这事
That's not what this is.
这不是私人恩怨
This isn't personal.
迪恩 我不是杀手
I'm not a killer, Dean.
我是猎手
I'm a hunter.
你弟就是我要猎杀的人
And your brother's fair game.
- 我想我不应该离开 - 阿瓦 我不想伤害你
- I don't think I should leave. - I want you out of harm's way, Ava.
- 那你呢？- 我做的从不是安全的事
- What about you? - Harm's way doesn't really bother me.
不要 你现在正照着我的预兆走
No, but you are walking right into my vision.
- 这样你会死的 - 我不在乎
- I mean, this is how you die. - Doesn't matter.
我要救我哥
It's my brother.
也许我能帮上忙
Maybe I can help.
你该做的都做了 只要回到你未婚夫身边就可以了
You've done all you can. Just-Just go back to your fiancé.
你肯定？
Are you sure?
是的 我肯定
Yes, I'm sure.
回家吧 阿瓦 那里是安全的
Go home, Ava. You'll be safe there.
只是…
Well, just…
保证在事办完后 打电话给我
promise me you'll call. When you get your brother…
就告诉我一切都没事
to let me know that everything's all right.
我保证
I promise.
我在路易斯安那州除了个魔鬼
See, I was doing an exorcism down in Louisiana.
是个十几岁的女孩 看上去没什么特别的 是个低级别的魔鬼
Teenage girl. Seemed routine, some low-level demon.
但在模糊的话语中
But between the jabbering and head-spinning…
那个魔鬼提到一些 关于即将到来的战争的事
damn thing muttered something. About a coming war.
我想那话并不是故意的 可能只是一时说漏了 但太晚了
I don't think it meant to. It just kind of slipped out, but it was too late.
那些话已经引起了我的兴趣
Piqued my interest.
如果你用对了工具 你真的可以和魔鬼沟通
And you can really make a demon talk, if you got the right tools.
那个被附身的女孩怎么样了？
What happened to the possessed girl?
她没有挺过来
She didn't make it.
你这狗娘养的
Well, you're a son of a bitch.
不准这么说我老妈
That's my mama you're talking about.
反正
Anyway…
那魔鬼告诉我 在即将到的战争中他们会有战士
this demon tells me they have soldiers to fight in this coming war.
人类将为魔鬼而战 你相信这些吗？
Humans, fighting on hell's side. Do you believe that?
他们能通神 所以已经不是真正的人类了
I mean, they're psychics, so they're not exactly pure humans but still-
什么样的人会残杀自己的同类啊？
What kind of worthless scumbag you gotta be to turn against your own race?
你知道最大的发现是什么？
But you know the biggest kick in the ass?
魔鬼告诉我其中一个还是我认识的
This demon said I knew one of them.
就是我们亲爱的萨姆·温彻斯特
Our very own Sammy Winchester.
这… 真是…
Oh, this is…
真是傻的不轻啊 就算是你我也这么说
This is a whole new level of moronic, even for you.
是吗？
Yeah.
别装傻了迪恩
Come on, Dean.
我知道有关萨姆能有预兆的事
I know… about Sam's visions.
- 我什么都知道 - 真的？
- I know everything. I know… - Really?
魔鬼告诉你的？是呀 他们不会说谎
Because a demon told you? Ha-ha. Yeah, and it wasn't lying.
嘿 迪恩 我可不是在雅虎上随便查查就了事的人
Hey, Dean, I'm not some reckless yahoo, okay?
我做足功课了 我他妈的可以确定这是真的
I did my homework. Made damn sure it was true.
听着 你可以在罗德豪斯拿到资料
Look, you got your Roadhouse connections…
我也有我的办法
I got mine.
这就是为什么 我能第一时间知道萨姆的所在
That's how I found Sammy in the first place.
一个月前 我发现这镇上有个他们的同类
About a month ago, I found another one of these freaks, here in town.
他只要一碰谁 谁就会电焦
He'd deep-fry a person just by touching them.
是吗 他杀了人？
Yeah, did he kill anyone?
没 除了丁克斯家的那只猫
Besides Mr. Tinkles, the cat? No.
但杀人也是迟早的事
But he was working up to it.
他们都会变成杀手 迪恩
They're all gonna be killers, Dean. We gotta take them all out.
我们要把他们全干掉 其中也包括萨姆
And that means Sammy too.
你以为萨姆会傻乎乎地到从前门直接进来？
Think Sam's stupid enough to go to the front door?
我可没那么想
No, I don't.
尤其是在你警告他之后
Especially since I'm sure you found a way to warn him.
你真以为我是傻子吗？
You really think I'm that stupid?
不是
No.
萨姆会先看一下这屋子
Sammy's gonna scope the place first.
看到我埋伏在前门
See me covering the front door.
他就会从后门进来
So he's gonna take the back.
如果他这样做了 他就会绊到那根电线
And when he does, he'll hit the tripwire.
接着… 。-
Then…
就爆炸
boom.
萨姆不会被那个电线绊倒的
Sam's not gonna fall for a frigging tripwire.
也许你说的没错
Maybe you're right.
所以我做了二手准备
That's why I'll have a second one.
听着
Hey, look.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真希望我不要那么做 我真的这么想
I wish I didn't have to do this, I really do.
但这样做是值得的
But for what it's worth…
一会儿就完事了
it'll be quick.
别这样 伙计
Come on, man.
我比任何人都了解萨姆
I know Sam, okay? Better than anyone.
他比我有良知的多
He's got more of a conscience than I do.
这家伙连看色情网站都觉得内疚
The guy feels guilty surfing Internet for porn.
也许你是对的
Maybe you're right.
- 但有一天他会变成怪兽 - 怎么变？嗯？
- But one day, he's gonna be a monster. - How? Huh?
像萨姆这样的人如何变成怪兽？
How does Sam become a monster?
- 问住我了 不过他肯定会变 - 不 你什么都不知道
- Beats me, but he will. - No, you don't know that.
我对你的表现表示吃惊 迪恩
I'm surprised at you, Dean.
那么感情用事
Getting all emotional.
我听到的你比现在要专业的多
I'd heard you were more of a professional than this.
听着 就算你独自开车到处跑
Look, let's say you were cruising around in that car of yours…
带着散弹枪去猎鬼 呃？
and, uh, you had little Hitler riding shotgun, right?
而他还是个蹩脚的书呆子
Back when he was just some goofy, crappy artist.
但你知道有一天他会变成什么
But you knew what he was gonna turn into someday.
你必须把他干掉 没问题了 好吗？
You'd take him out. No questions. Am I right?
- 那不是萨姆 - 他就是那样的
- That's not Sam. - Yes, it is.
只是你还没看出来而已
You just can't see it yet.
迪恩 这是他的命运
Dean, it's his destiny.
听着
Look…
对此我也表示同情
I'm sympathetic.
他是你弟弟 你所爱的人
He's your brother. You love the guy.
这样做对你来说会痛不欲生
This has gotta hurt like hell for you.
但这么说吧
But here's the thing.
本来早该灭了他的
It would've wrecked him.
但是有你父亲在…
But your dad…
如果他必须那么做的话 他肯定也会铁下心来 做我现在做的事
if it came right down to it, he'd have the stones to do the right thing here.
你告诉我
Are you telling me…
你成不像了你父亲那样的人吗？
you're not the man he is?
你听到了吗？
You hear him?
他来了
Here he comes.
等一下
Hold on.
还没完呢
Not yet.
让我们等着瞧吧
Just wait and see.
对不起了 迪恩
Sorry, Dean.
放下枪
Drop the gun.
你不应该在这里脱鞋子
Shouldn't take your shoes off around here.
- 你可能会得破伤风的 - 快把枪放下
- You might get tetanus. - Put it down now!
你不会杀我的 不是吗？萨姆？
You wouldn't shoot me, would you, Sammy?
因为你哥说你是个圣人
Because your brother, he thinks you're some kind of saint.
是的 但我不能确定
Yeah? Well, I wouldn't be so sure.
看到吗 我说的没错吧
See, that's what I said.
你比你猎杀的怪物好不到哪去
You're no better than the filthy things you hunt.
开枪吧
Do it.
开枪呀 萨姆让你哥也知道你其实就是个杀手
Do it! Show your brother the killer you really are, Sammy.
是萨姆
It's Sam.
- 婊子养的 - 迪恩 不要
- Son of a… - Dean, no.
第一次就不该饶他 我可不想再饶他一次
I let him live once. I won't make the same mistake twice.
相信我
Trust me.
戈登已经被「搞定」了
Gordon's taken care of.
快走
Come on.
这就是你所谓的「照顾」？
You call this "taken care of"?
- 你到底做了什么？- 相信我吧
- What the hell are we doing? - Just trust me on this.
放下不的武器 跪下
Drop your weapons. Get down on your knees.
现在就做
Do it now.
双手放在头上
Hands above your head now!
现在跪在地上
On the ground, right now!
快做
Do it.
把手放在你的头上
Put your hands on your head.
现在放松
Easy, now.
看这个 看看这个 伙计们
Look at this. Look at this, guys.
匿名举报
Anonymous tip.
萨姆 你真是个「又好又出色的」市民
You're a fine, upstanding citizen, Sam.
- 戈登猎杀萨姆？- 他差点杀了我们
- Gordon Walker was hunting Sam? - He almost killed us.
- 你那里的人就不能闭上嘴少说话吗？- 你真以为是我
- Somebody can't keep her mouth shut. - And you honestly think it was me?
阿什或是乔出卖了你们？这不可能
Or Ash, or Jo? No way.
萨姆的事还有谁知道 嗯？你肯定和谁说过我们的事
Who else knows about Sam, huh? You must've been talking to somebody.
你可以说我们如何不好 但我们知道什么是诚实
You can say a lot of things about us, but we aren't disloyal…
而且我们也不是白痴 也从来提都没提过这事
and we're not stupid. We haven't breathed a word of this.
埃伦 戈登说他在罗德豪斯也有人
Gordon said he had Roadhouse connections.
但罗德豪斯里还有很多其它的捕猎者
And this roadhouse is full of other hunters.
他们也不笨 他们也是不错的猎捕者
They're all smart, they're good trackers…
每个都有他们的搭挡和消息来源
each of them with their own patterns and connections.
我现在就可以说出
Hell, I could name 12 of them…
一打能打听到这事的人
right now that are capable of putting this together.
对发生的一切我表示抱歉 迪恩
I am sorry about what happened, Dean.
但我不能左右这些人
But I can't control these people.
和他们的思想
Or what they choose to believe.
嘿 阿瓦 还是我 萨姆
Hey, Ava. It's Sam again, um.
如果听到我的留言请回我电话 只是想确认你已经到家了
Call me when you get this. Just wanna make sure you got home okay.
好了 再见
All right, bye.
一切都好？
Everything all right?
我希望如此
Yeah, I hope so.
戈登肯定要在里面至少蹲上几年
Well, Gordon should be reaching for the soap for the next few years at least.
是的 如果斯科特·凯里的死也算在他头上的话
Yeah.If they pin Scott Carey's murder on him.
他就别想出来了
And if he doesn't bust out.
老兄 以后别再这样做了？
Dude, if you ever take off like that again…
什么？
What?
你要杀了我？
You'll kill me?
- 那可一点也不好笑 - 知道了
- That's so not funny. - All right.
知道了 那下一站去哪？
All right, so where to next then?
- 一个词 阿姆斯特丹 - 迪恩
- One word. Amsterdam. - Dean
听说那里的咖啡店都没咖啡卖
I hear the coffee shops don't even serve coffee.
- 我可不想放下工作 - 去他的工作
- I'm not gonna just ditch the job. - Screw the job.
去他的 我已经对这工作厌倦了
Screw it. I'm sick of the job.
干这又没钱拿 又没人谢我们 唯一得到的就是坏运气
We don't get paid, we don't get thanked. Only thing we get's bad luck.
别这样 你是个猎手 你以前不是一直这样认为
Well, come on, dude. You're a hunter. It's what you were meant to do.
我可不相信什么命运的鬼话
I wasn't meant to do anything. I don't believe in that crap.
你是说你不相信我的命运？
You mean you don't believe in my destiny.
随你的便
Well, whatever.
听着 迪恩 以前我一直想逃避
Look, Dean, I've tried running before.
我逃到加利福尼亚 你看又发生了什么
I ran all the way to California, and look what happened.
你不能就这样逃避 这样也保护不了我
You can't run from this. And you can't protect me.
我可以试一下
I can try.
谢了
Thanks for that.
听着 迪恩 我还要继续猎捕
Look, Dean, I'm gonna keep hunting.
不管接着会发生什么 我都会义无反顾的去做
I mean, whatever is coming, I'm taking it head-on.
如果你真想照顾我的话 那你就要跟紧一点
So if you really want to watch my back, I guess you'll have to stick around.
- 贱人 - 怪胎
- Bitch. - Jerk.
又打电话给那个叫阿瓦的女孩？你和他有暧昧？
You're calling that Ava girl again? Are you sweet on her or something?
- 她已经订婚了 迪恩 - 所以… ？
- She's engaged, Dean. - So?
关键在于你要想拯救世界 就一刻也不能闲？
What's the point of saving the world if you can't get a little nookie?
什么？
What?
我有不详的感觉
Just a feeling.
这里离皮奥里亚有多远？
How far is it to Peoria?
哈喽？
Hello?
有人在家吗？
Is anybody home?
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
嘿
Hey.
硫磺
Sulphur.
有魔鬼来过这
Demon's been here.
阿瓦
Ava.